<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.jdownloader.JDownloader</id>
  <name>JDownloader</name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <developer_name>Appwork GmbH</developer_name>
  <summary>Download management tool</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Ferramenta de gerenciamento de download</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Descargar herramienta de gestión</summary>
  <description><p>JDownloader is a free download management tool with a huge community of developers that makes downloading as easy and fast as it should be. Users can start, stop or pause downloads, set bandwidth limitations, auto-extract archives and much more. It's an easy-to-extend frameworkthat can save hours of your valuable time every day!</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="pt_BR"><p>JDownloader é uma ferramenta de gerenciamento de download gratuito com uma enorme comunidade de desenvolvedores que faz o download tão fácil e rápido quanto deveria ser. Os usuários podem iniciar, parar ou pausar downloads, definir limitações de largura de banda, extrair arquivos automaticamente e muito mais. É um framework fácil de estender que pode economizar horas do seu precioso tempo todos os dias!</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="es"><p>JDownloader es una herramienta gratuita de administración de descargas con una gran comunidad de desarrolladores que hace que la descarga sea tan fácil y rápida como debería ser. Los usuarios pueden iniciar, detener o pausar descargas, establecer limitaciones de ancho de banda, extraer automáticamente archivos y mucho más. ¡Es un marco fácil de ampliar que puede ahorrar horas de su valioso tiempo todos los días!</p></description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.jdownloader.org/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="pt_BR">http://www.jdownloader.org/pt/home/index?s=lng_pt</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="es">http://www.jdownloader.org/es/home/index?s=lng_es</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://jdownloader.org/_media/screenshots/ss-2009.08.15-11.18.36.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.0" date="2011-01-01"/>
  </releases>
</component>
